Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 3 and District 3 Locals, 1936-1990s UE.4.1.3
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 3 Locals, 2.
  - Local 301
    - Local 301 Outgoing Correspondence, 1936-1954 (Box 3, Folder 65)
      - Marshall White to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, December 23, 1952; 1.
      - White to Emspak Regarding Dues, January 29, 1954; 2.
      - Local 301 Executive Board to W. R. Burrows Regarding Local 301 General Electric Strikes, 1936; 3.
      - Local 301 Executive Board to David Lilienthal Regarding Atomic Energy Commission and Anti-communism, October 25, 1948; 4.
    - Local 301 Schenectady Correspondence, February 12, 1952-June 11, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Local 301 Financial Vouchers, April 18-June 16, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 67)
      - Jacob Maracchion, April 18, 1954; 1.
      - Gerald Tooke, April 19, 1954; 2.
      - Harris Dean, April 21, 1954; 3.
      - Anthony Calabrese, April 26, 1954; 4.
      - William Siler, April 30, 1954; 5.
      - Calabrase, May 1, 1954; 6.
      - Dean, May 1, 1954; 7.
      - Maracchion, May 1, 1954; 8.
      - Victor Teich, May 3, 1954; 9.
      - Tooke, May 14, 1954; 10.
      - Teich, May 16, 1954; 11.
      - Maracchion, May 15, 1954; 12.
      - Dean, May 16, 1954; 13.
      - Siler, June 1, 1954; 14.
      - Dean, June 1, 1954; 15.
      - Maracchion, June 1, 1954; 16.
      - Raymond Metzinger, June 1-3, 1954; 17-18.
      - Teich, June 1, 1954; 19.
      - Tooke, June 1, 1954; 20.
      - McKinley Wheeler, June 15, 1954; 21.
      - Teich, June 16, 1954; 22.
      - Maracchion, June 15, 1954; 23.
      - Dean, June 16, 1954; 24.
    - Local 301 Financial Vouchers, June 16-July 9, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 68)
      - Gerald Tooke, June 16, 1954; 1.
      - McKinley Wheeler, June 27, 1954; 2.
      - Harris Dean, June 30, 1954; 3.
      - Robert Donley, June 27, 1954; 4.
      - Robert Needleman, June 30-July 28, 1954; 5-9.
      - Donley, July 11, 1954; 10.
      - Needleman, August 8-September 1, 1954; 11-14.
      - Vincent Perillo, July 9, 1954; 15.
    - Local 301 Financial, 1940-1951 (Box 3, Folder 69)
      - Per Capita Payments, 1940; 1.
      - Statement of Income and Expenses, December 1950; 2.
      - Ledger, March 19-April 22, 1951; 3.
    - Local 301 Ledgers, March 7-April 3, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 70)
      - Ledger, March 1-April 12, 1954; 1-2.
      - Ledger with March 21, 1954, Dave Letter to Janet, March 7-21, 1954; 3.
      - Ledger with March 29, 1954 Dave Letter to Janet, 4.
      - Ledger with April 3, 1954, David Ratner Letter to Janet Barish, March 29, 1954; 5.
      - Ledger, April 3, 1954; 6.
    - Local 301 Organizers Cash Book, April 1954 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Local 301 Financial, April-May 1954 (Box 3, Folder 72)
      - Indemnity Bond, April 1954; 1.
      - Ledger with April 26, 1954, David Ratner Letter to Janet, April 10, 1954; 2.
      - Ledger with May 4, 1954, Ratner Letter to Janet, April 25, 1954; 3.
      - Ledger with May 14, 1954, Ratner Letter to Janet, May 4, 1954; 4.
    - Local 301 Ledgers, May 14-19, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 73)
      - Ledger with May 29, 1954, David Ratner Letter to Janet, May 14, 1954; 1.
      - Ledger with May 28, 1954, Ratner Letter to Janet, May 19, 1954; 2.
    - Local 301 Ledgers, June 1954 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Local 301 Ledgers, June 12-29, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 75)
      - Ledger with June 18, 1954, David Ratner Letter to Janet, June 12, 1954; 1.
      - Ledgers, June 20-29, 1954; 2-3.
    - Local 301 Ledger, June 26, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Local 301 Workers Council, May 1, 1934-August 1, 1935 (Box 3, Folder 77)
      - Primary Election, May 1, 1934; 1.
      - Workers Council Minutes, March 7, 1935; 2.
      - Report of Executive Committee, March 7, 1935; 3.
      - Brief, March 12, 1935; 4.
      - Minutes, May 2, 1935; 5.
      - Executive Committee Report, May 2, 1935; 6.
      - Minutes, June 6, 1935; 7.
      - Executive Committee Report, June 6, 1935; 8.
      - Minutes, July 8, 1935; 9.
      - Executive Committee Report, July 8-August 1, 1935; 10-11.
    - Local 301 Workers Council, August 1, 1935-May 21, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 78)
      - Minutes, August 1, 1935; 1.
      - Executive Committee Report, August 1935; 2.
      - Minutes, September 5-November 7, 1935; 3-5.
      - Special Meeting Minutes, 1935; 6.
      - Questions to be Discussed by Mr. Swope, 1935; 7.
      - Workers Council Election, May 21, 1936; 8.
    - Local 301 Organization, November 1, 1935-September 29, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 79)
      - James Matles to National Labor Relations Board, November 1, 1935; 1.
      - Elinore Herrick to James Matles, November 4, 1935; 2.
      - National Labor Relations Board Brief, November 6, 1935; 3.
      - Herrick to Matles, November 21, 1935; 4.
      - Matles to Federation of Metal and Allied Unions, November 23, 1935; 5.
      - Herrick to Matles, November 25, 1935; 6.
      - Draft Letter to National Labor Relations Board, November 1935; 7.
      - Matles to Herrick, December 27, 1935; 8.
      - Committee Men Meeting Minutes, May 5, 1936; 9.
      - Note to General Electric Workers, May 1936; 10.
      - Facts Concerning the Stoppage in Bulding 12, May 136; 11.
      - Local 301 to Council Men, May 29, 1936; 12.
      - James Carey to Julius Emspak, June 4, 1936; 13.
      - Carey Telegram to Frances Perkins, June 5, 1936; 14.
      - Lee Telegram to Gardner Jackson, June 6, 1936; 15.
      - Carey Telegram to Emspak, June 8, 1936; 16.
      - Emspak Telegram to David Moscowitz, September 24, 1936; 17.
      - Emspak to John D. Moore, September 29, 1936; 18.
    - Local 301 Organization, 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 80)
      - Julius Emspak to John Moore, October 21, 1936; 1.
      - Election Plans, December 1936; 2.
      - What Divisions Should Do, December 1936; 3.
      - Strike Facts Sheet, 1936; 4.
      - Tom Wright Summary, 1936; 5.
      - Union and Works Council Meeting Minutes, 1936; 6.
      - Committe Men's Meeting, January 26, 1937; 7.
      - Leo Jandreau to Brothers, February 18, 1937; 8.
    - Local 301 Organization, August 20, 1937-May 25, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 81)
      - Progress Report, May 8, 1937; 1.
      - E. O. Schreve to James Carey, August 20, 1937; 2.
      - Carey to Schreve, August 24, 1937; 3.
      - Post Comnissioner to James Matles, August 25, 1937; 4.
      - Elinore Herrick to Julius Emspak, January 6-February 11, 1938; 5-6.
      - Leo Jandreau to Brothers, February 25, 1938; 7.
      - Call to Conference of Local 301 with Discussion Outline, May 25, 1938; 8.
    - Local 301 Organization, June 8-September 21, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 82)
      - Recommendations to Conference, June 8, 1938; 1.
      - Local 301 Executive Board to Brothers, September 21, 1938; 2.
    - Local 301 Farmers, February 3-25, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 83)
      - Carl Bogardus to John Brophy, February 3, 1937; 1.
      - Brophy to Bogardus, February 15, 1937; 2.
      - Katherine Pollack to James Carey, February 15, 1937; 3.
      - Julius Emspak to Bogardus, February 19, 1937; 4.
      - Emspak to Leo Jandreau, February 19, 1937; 5.
      - Bogardus to Emspak, February 19, 1937; 6.
      - Emspak to Jandreau, February 25, 1937; 7.
      - Emspak to Bogardus, February 25, 1937; 8.
    - Local 301 Grievances, January 4, 1937-December 19, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 84)
      - Docket Number 605 Regarding Women and Unemployment, January 4, 1937; 1.
      - Docket Number 218 Regarding Women Vacation, April 15, 1937; 2.
      - Docket Number 267 Regarding Hours and Health, May 4, 1937; 3.
      - Docket Number 289 Regarding Vacation, Unemployment and Women, May 12, 1937; 4.
      - Docket Number 532 Regarding Unemployment and Women, September 14, 1937; 5.
      - Docket Number 620 Regarding Women and Unemployment, January 20, 1937; 6.
      - Docket Number 621 Regarding Women and Unemployment, January 20, 1937; 7.
      - Docket Number 687 Regarding Seniority and Promotions, October 6, 1938; 8.
      - Docket Number 684 Regarding Job Classification, October 24, 1938; 9.
      - Leo Jandreau Letter to Julius Emspak Regarding Job Classification, November 21, 1938; 10.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Women, November 21, 1938; 11.
      - Docket Number 695 Regarding Wages and Unemployment, November 25, 1938; 12.
      - Docket Number 694 Regarding Overtime, November 23, 1938; 13.
      - Docket Number 698 Regarding Apprenticeship and Unemployment, November 30, 1938; 14.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Wages, November 30, 138; 15.
      - Docket Number 706 Regarding Seniority, December 9, 1938; 16.
      - Leo Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Unemployment, December 9, 1938; 17.
      - Docket Number 705 Regarding Unemployment and Seniority, December 9, 1938; 18.
      - Docket Number 715 Regarding Unemployment and Seniority, December 19, 1938; 19.
    - Local 301 Grievances, January 24-February 16, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 85)
      - Leo Jandreau to Julius Emspak, January 24, 1939; 1.
      - Jandreau to Emspak Regarding Unemployment, January 30, 1939; 2.
      - Statistics of Cases Discussed with Union Executive Board in 1938, February 16, 1939; 3.
    - Local 301 Malecki Health Case, April 29-June 7, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 86)
      - Maria Soroborska to James Carey, April 29, 1937; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Soroborska, May 5, 1937; 2.
      - Soroborska to Emspak, May 28, 1937; 3.
      - Emspak to Soroboska, June 7, 1937; 4.
    - Local 301 Drafting Employees, May 9, 1941-July 20, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 87)
      - Constitution and By-laws of the Schenectady Draftsmen's Association, May 9, 1941-March 30, 1942; 1-2.
      - Unsigned Letter to Jesse Lane, April 16, 1942; 3.
      - Edwin Beal to Lane, April 24, 1942; 4.
      - National Labor Relations Board Petition, June 3, 1942; 5.
      - National Labor Relations Board Notice of Postponement, July 16, 1942; 6.
      - Notice of Hearing, July 14, 1942; 7.
      - Julius Emspak to Beal, July 20, 1942; 8.
    - Local 301 Drafting Employees, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 88)
      - National Labor Relations Board Hearing Notes, 1942; 1-2.
      - Rene Richtmeyer to Miss Wallingford with Blank Membership Application, 1942; 3.
    - Local 301 Labor Day Celebration, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 89)
      - S. M. Vottis Letter, 1.
      - Program, 2.
      - Vottis Letter, August 23, 1943; 3.
      - Schenectady Union Star and Schenectady Gazette Labor Day Celebration Newspaper Clippings, August 17-September 7, 1943; 4.
    - Local 301 Toolmakers War Labor Board Case, October 11, 1940-October 13, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 90)
      - Leo Jandreau to Locals 119, 255, 286, 301, 320, 422, 506, 901, UER and United Mine Workers of America, October 13, 1943; 1.
      - Supplementary Statement by the Union, October 13, 1943; 2.
      - Exhibit A, July 26, 1943; 3.
      - Exhibit B, July 26, 1943; 4.
      - Exhibit C-1, September 6, 1943; 5.
      - Exhibit C-2, May 11, 1943; 6.
      - Exhibit C-3, January 13, 1941; 7.
      - Exhibit C-4, October 11, 1940; 8.
      - Exhibit C-5, April 8, 1941; 9.
      - Exhibit C-6, February 4, 1943; 10.
      - Exhibit C-7, April 26, 1943; 11.
      - Exhibit C-8, August 18, 1943; 12.
      - Exhibit C-9, October 16, 1942; 13.
      - Exhibit C-10, January 7, 1942; 14.
      - Exhibit C-11, May 7, 1943; 15.
      - Exhibit C-12, October 21, 1942; 16.
    - Local 301 Kersten Commitee Hearings, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 91)
      - WSNY 9 Script, September 22, 1948; 1.
      - WSNY 9 Radio Broadcast Script, September 29, 1948; 2.
      - Local 301 Fights Back, October 1948; 3.
      - We Protest, 1948; 4.
      - Petition, 1948; 5.
    - Local 301 Schenectady Stanton vs. Peterson, November 1947-January 1948 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Local 301 National Subsidy and Expenses, December 21, 1949-January 19, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 93)
      - James Matles to Leo Jandreau, December 21, 1949; 1.
      - Michael Jimenez to Matles, December 29, 1949; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to George Stillman with November 11, 1949, Local 301 Loans, March 3, 1950; 3.
      - Empsak to Irving Simon, March 3, 1950; 4.
      - David Ratner to Simon, March 9, 1950; 5.
      - Emspak to Austin Emgraves, April 21, 1950; 6.
      - Emspak to Schenectady Printing Company, April 21, 1950; 7.
      - Emspak to Teddy's, April 21, 1950; 8.
      - Emspak to Schenectady Printing, May 11-19, 1950; 9-10.
      - Emspak to W.P.T.R. Station, May 22, 1950; 11.
      - Rudy Radosevich to Ratner, May 22, 1950; 12.
      - Patroon Broadcasting to UE, May 23, 1950; 13.
      - Emspak to Schenectady Printing, May 29, 1950; 14.
      - Janet Barish to Radosevich with June 30, 1950, Expense List, July 20, 150; 15.
      - Jandreau to David Scribner, November 6, 1950; 16.
      - Scribner to Jandreau, November 8, 1950; 17.
      - Emspak to Jandreau, December 1, 1950; 18.
      - Jandreau to Emspak, December 4, 1950; 19.
      - Emspak to Jandreau, December 5, 1951; 20.
      - Marshall White to Emspak, January 18, 1951; 21.
      - White to Scribner, January 18, 1951; 22.
      - Emspak to White, January 19, 1951; 23.
    - Local 301 National Subsidy and Expenses, January 24, 1951-September 10, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 94)
      - David Ratner to Marshall White, January 24, 1951; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Leo Jandreau, September 10, 1952; 2.
      - Statement, 3.
      - Taxes, 4.
    - Local 301 McCarthy Committee, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 95)
      - Dear Friend, June 18, 1953; 1.
      - Statement, 1953; 2.
    - Local 301 Inter-union Rivalry, March 4-May 8, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 96)
      - James Carey to Leo Jandreau, March 4, 1954; 1.
      - Jandreau to Carey, March 5, 1954; 2.
      - March Union Dues Statement, March 12, 1954; 3.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to A.C. Stevens, March 23, 1954; 4.
      - Ernest Kopper to All Turbine Stewards, March 31, 1954; 5.
      - Helen Quirini to All General Electric Workers, April 1, 1954; 6.
      - Kopper to All Local 301 Members, April 2, 1954; 7.
      - April Dues, April 20, 1954; 8.
      - Rachel to Janet, April 20, 1954; 9.
      - Rachel to Emma, April 27, 1954; 10.
      - Rachel Letter to Emma with James Matles Letter to Anthony Calabresa and Matles Letter to Gerald Tooke, April 28, 1954; 11.
      - Vincent DeLeo Letter, May 3, 1954; 12.
      - Kopper to Local 301 Members, May 6-May 8, 1954; 13-17.
    - Local 301 Inter-union Rivalry, May 11-August 24, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 97)
      - Ernest Kopper to Local 301 Members, May 11, 1954; 1.
      - Rachel to Janet, May 14, 1954; 2.
      - Dues, May 19, 1954; 3.
      - Rachel to Emma, June 16, 1954; 4.
      - Leo Jandreau to Albert Fitzgerald, July 30, 1954; 5.
      - Fitzgerald to Thomas Flanagan, July 30, 1954; 6.
      - Bernice Gouthey to Members, August 19, 1954; 7.
      - Harold Hall to UE, August 19, 1954; 8.
      - Pending Litigation, August 24, 1954; 9.
    - Local 301 Correspondence, Management Statement and Report, January 28, 1938-June 21, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 98)
      - Julius Emspak to Whom It May Concern Regarding Local 301 Officers, January 28, 1938; 1.
      - Schulte-Jandreau Telephone Conversation Regarding Wages, September 10, 1940; 2.
      - Jandreau-Burrows Meeting Regarding Wages and Toolmakers, January 24, 1941; 3.
      - Statement by Management Regarding Subcontracting, February 13, 1941; 4.
      - Report of Dues Status, June 21, 1941; 5.
      - Leo Jandreau Letter Regarding Local 301 Picnic with Raffle Tickets, 1941; 6.
    - Local 301 Correspondence, Maintenance Clause Reports and Questionnaire, November 18, 1942-July 12, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 99)
      - July Maintenance Clause Report, November 18, 1942; 1.
      - April-June Maintenance Clause Report, December 30, 1942; 2.
      - August Maintenance Clause Report, January 23, 1943; 3.
      - Leo Jandreau to All Executive Board Members Regarding Stewards, March 8, 1943; 4.
      - A Message From the Citizen Unity Committee to Schenectady's Civic-minded Citizens, May 19, 1943; 5.
      - Women's Questionnaire, May 1943; 6.
      - Bevlah Burhoe to Julius Emspak Regarding Russian War Relief, July 12, 1943; 7.
    - Local 301 Correspondence, December 31, 1943-March 14, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 100)
      - What Our Public Relations Program Means to Local 301, December 31, 1943; 1.
      - Russ Nixon to S.A. Archer Regarding Firings and Blacklist, January 12, 1944; 2.
      - Vincent Maloney to Brothers Regarding Factionalism with March 14, 1944, Membership Resolution, March 16, 1944; 3.
    - Local 301 Correspondence, Jandreau Brief, Reports and Statement, September 3, 1947-May 15, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 101)
      - Andrew Peterson to Julius Emspak Regarding Women, Dismissal and Working Conditions with Stewards Resolution, September 3, 1947; 1.
      - James Matles to H.C. Lipides Regarding Staff Members, March 24, 1949; 2.
      - Rufus Peret to UE Regarding American Arbitration Association, June 13, 1949; 3.
      - Leo Jandreau Brief Regarding Communism, 1950; 4.
      - William Kelly Statement Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, September 14, 1951; 5.
      - Report of Local 301 Delegates Attending National Wage Conference, April 1952; 6.
      - Statement on Collective Bargaining, March 16-17, 1953; 7.
      - Western New York UE Wage Conference Committee, May 22, 1953; 8.
      - District 3 and 4 Womens Contivation Committee Minutes, May 15, 1953; 9.
    - Local 301 Correspondence, Forms, Statements, Notes and Agreement, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 102)
      - The Record Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1954; 1.
      - Alex Kotaiski Statement to "My Fellow Workres" Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, 1954; 2.
      - Joseph Dermody to "the General Electric Company", 1954; 3.
      - Albert Fitzgerald Telegram to Leo Jandreau, 1954; 4.
      - Statement Regarding Schenectady General Electric, 5.
      - Dues Form, 6.
      - Pledge Petition, 7.
      - Resolution Regarding Local 301 General Electric Strikes, 8.
      - Committee Unemployment Notes, 9.
      - Notes on General Electric Steam-fitters Strike and Steam-fitters Inter-union Rivalry, 10.
      - Agreement Regarding Local 301 Steam-fitters, 11.
    - Local 301 Executive Board Officers Report, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Local 301 Financial Secretary S.M. Vottis Report, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Local 301 Leo Jandreau Officer Report, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Local 301 Officers Reports, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Officers Report with Late Survey, January 19, 1940, Leo Jandreau Letter to James Matles and January 23, 1940, Jandreau Letter to Matles, 1939; 1.
    - Local 301 Electrical Union News, September 1939-May 1942 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Local 301 Electrical Union News, May 30-August 1, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Local 301 Electrical Union News, August 23, 1942-April 9, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Local 301 Electrical Union News, July 16, 1948-January 21, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Local 301 Electrical Union News, January 28-September 9, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Local 301 Electrical Union News, December 1950-May 1954 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Local 301 Schenectady IUE CIO News, May 5, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Local 301 Local 301 News, May 7-August 20, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Local 301 Labor News, May 20-December 8, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Local 301 Works News, September 11, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Local 301 Pamphlets, 1936-1944 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Are You With Us? Regarding Organization, 1936; 1.
      - Unemploymetn & Speed-Ups! Regarding Organization, 1936; 2.
      - Organize Now, 1936; 3.
      - Learn How The Strike Is Winning Regarding Local 301 RCA, 1936; 4.
      - Are You Doing Your Part Regarding Organization, 1936; 5.
      - The American Way Is The Union Way, 1936; 6.
      - CIO Answers Enemies, 1937; 7.
      - Town Hall Meetings, 1943; 8.
      - Greetings to the Officers and Professional Workers, 1944; 9.
      - An Open Letter to You regarding White Collar Workers, 1944; 10.
    - Local 301 Pamphlets, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Advertise Regarding Finances with November 2, 1944, Austin Case Letter to Julius Emspak, 1.
    - Local 301 Annual Report and Directory, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Local 301 Pamphlets, 1946-1954 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - A Statement Regarding General Electric Strikes, February 7, 1946; 1.
      - Mr. Boulware and the Record Regarding General Electric Collective Bargaining, November 21, 1947; 2.
      - GE Wages and GE Prices Regarding Inflation, January 30, 1948; 3.
      - Fighting Wage Policy Regarding Election and Local 301 Officers, 1949; 4.
      - Questions & Answers Concerning Attack in UE Regarding Anti-communism, January 1953; 5.
      - GE Calls on UnAmericans Again Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1954; 6.
      - UE 301 Information Bulletin Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1954; 7.
    - Local 301 Leaflets, 1936-1942 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - To Schenectady Work Employees Regarding Grievances and General Electric Schenectady Organization, June 1936; 1.
      - Clambake, August 1936; 2.
      - GE Refuse Wage Increase! Regarding Schenectady General Electric, September 15, 1936; 3.
      - Toolsmaker's Night Regarding Schenectady General Electric, September 17, 1936; 4.
      - Dear Brother Regarding Schenectady General Electric, October 8, 1936; 5.
      - Special Notice Regarding Local 301 General Electric Strikes, 1936; 6.
      - All GE Workers Regarding Local 301 General Electric Strikes and Wages, June 1936; 7.
      - Regional Labor Board Enters Helping Union Leaders Regarding National Labor Relations Board and Schenectady General Electric, 1936; 8.
      - To All GE Employees Regarding Local 301 RCA, 1936; 9.
      - Union Mass Meeting Regarding Schenectady General Electric and Wages, 1936; 10.
      - Union Victory Regarding Speed-up, Wages and Schenectady General Electric, 1936; 11.
      - Profits for GE!, 1937; 12.
      - Join Your Union!, 1937; 13.
      - UE Defends America Regarding Young Communist League with September 16, 1941, Leo Jandreau Letter to Julius Emspak, 14.
      - To The Members of Local 301 Regarding Membership Maintenance, 1942; 15.
    - Local 301 Leaflets, 1945-1954 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Mass Meeting Regarding Wages, 1945; 1.
      - Newspapers Against the People, September 29, 1948; 2.
      - Convention Extra Regarding UE 1949 Convention, September 20-11, 1949; 3-6.
      - Carey Support Break Up 301 Membership Meeting, November 18, 1949; 7.
      - High Prices Can Come Down, 1949; 8.
      - Dear Brothers & Sisters Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, September 8, 1951; 9.
      - UE 301 Schenectady Election, September 5, 1951; 10.
      - What They Say About the Un-American Witchunts, 1953; 11.
      - When and How It Happend Regarding Wages and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, 1953; 12.
      - While UE Members Fought Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, March 9, 1954; 13.
      - Spilling The Beans Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, March 10, 1954; 14.
      - UE Is Exclusive Barganing Agent, March 31, 1954; 15.
      - Turbine News Letter, April 1, 1954; 16.
      - Shop Workers Bulletin, April 2, 1954; 17.
      - Attention Building 285, April 1954; 18.
      - Turbine News Letter, May 4, 1954; 19.
      - UE Facts for Action, May 4, 1954; 20.
    - Local 301 Leaflets, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - A & O Bulletin, May 5, 1954; 1.
      - Electronic Flash, May 5, 1954; 2.
      - UE Fighting Farming Out 107 Jobs, May 5, 1954; 3-4.
      - Turbine News Letter, May 7, 1954; 5-7.
      - No Politics With Turbine Grievances, May 7, 1954; 8.
      - UE Womens Conference, May 8, 1954; 9.
      - Information Bulletin, May 10, 1954; 10.
      - Porcelain Bulletin, May 10, 1954; 11.
      - Racetrack News, May 10, 1954; 12.
      - Unity Committee, May 10, 1954; 13.
      - Protect Our Jobs, May 10, 1954; 14.
      - Information Bulletin, May 10, 1954; 15-16.
      - Missing- $118,000, May 11, 1954; 17.